let questions8 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "anniversary",
      answer: "C. Jahrestag",
      options: [
        "A. Geburtstag",
        "B. Feiertag",
        "C. Jahrestag",
        "D. Festtag"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "arithmetic",
      answer: "A. Arithmetik",
      options: [
        "A. Arithmetik",
        "B. Geometrie",
        "C. Algebra",
        "D. Physik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "ashamed",
      answer: "D. beschämt",
      options: [
        "A. stolz",
        "B. glücklich",
        "C. zufrieden",
        "D. beschämt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to burst",
      answer: "B. platzen",
      options: [
        "A. brechen",
        "B. platzen",
        "C. fallen",
        "D. reißen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "carpenter",
      answer: "C. Tischler",
      options: [
        "A. Maurer",
        "B. Maler",
        "C. Tischler",
        "D. Klempner"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "coal",
      answer: "A. Kohle",
      options: [
        "A. Kohle",
        "B. Holz",
        "C. Stein",
        "D. Sand"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "couch",
      answer: "D. Sofa",
      options: [
        "A. Stuhl",
        "B. Sessel",
        "C. Hocker",
        "D. Sofa"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to drip",
      answer: "B. tropfen",
      options: [
        "A. fließen",
        "B. tropfen",
        "C. gießen",
        "D. spritzen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "elegant",
      answer: "C. elegant",
      options: [
        "A. schlicht",
        "B. einfach",
        "C. elegant",
        "D. gewöhnlich"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "fabric",
      answer: "A. Stoff",
      options: [
        "A. Stoff",
        "B. Leder",
        "C. Plastik",
        "D. Metall"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "highlands",
      answer: "D. Hochland",
      options: [
        "A. Tiefland",
        "B. Tal",
        "C. Ebene",
        "D. Hochland"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "ivory",
      answer: "B. Elfenbein",
      options: [
        "A. Knochen",
        "B. Elfenbein",
        "C. Horn",
        "D. Marmor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "mill",
      answer: "C. Mühle",
      options: [
        "A. Fabrik",
        "B. Werkstatt",
        "C. Mühle",
        "D. Scheune"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "needle",
      answer: "A. Nadel",
      options: [
        "A. Nadel",
        "B. Schere",
        "C. Faden",
        "D. Knopf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to polish",
      answer: "D. polieren",
      options: [
        "A. putzen",
        "B. waschen",
        "C. reinigen",
        "D. polieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to sew",
      answer: "B. nähen",
      options: [
        "A. stricken",
        "B. nähen",
        "C. häkeln",
        "D. weben"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "shed",
      answer: "C. Schuppen",
      options: [
        "A. Garage",
        "B. Stall",
        "C. Schuppen",
        "D. Keller"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "thread",
      answer: "A. Faden",
      options: [
        "A. Faden",
        "B. Seil",
        "C. Schnur",
        "D. Wolle"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to trim",
      answer: "D. kürzen",
      options: [
        "A. schneiden",
        "B. rasieren",
        "C. scheren",
        "D. kürzen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "upwards",
      answer: "B. aufwärts",
      options: [
        "A. abwärts",
        "B. aufwärts",
        "C. seitwärts",
        "D. vorwärts"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
export default questions8;